checkmyemails.co 2016-03-19

# CheckAnyEmail - Access All Your Emails Fast & Easy with One Click!

< Back To The App!

**Effective January 1 2014**

This Privacy Policy outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected via this Website and the business operations of checkmyemails.co. 

Checkmyemails.co (via http://checkmyemails.co) provides this Privacy Policy to help users, customers and suppliers of the business make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website and business services of checkmyemails.co. 

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. "CHECKMYEMAILS.CO" DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

This Privacy Policy applies to checkmyemails.co' collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by checkmyemails.co on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Website"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to checkmyemails.co' other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. checkmyemails.co is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third web sites or applications. By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Website Terms of Use. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official checkmyemails.co contacts remain subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use and/or other stated policies. 

1\. Collection of Information. 

1.1 Information Collection By Survey. 

Checkmyemails.co collects information, personal and otherwise, from individuals primarily by having the individuals provide that information directly to checkmyemails.co through its surveys and other opportunities to share information. Information collection may happen by various methods, including, but not limited to, an individual who transmits or receives a message through a checkmyemails.co web site by any means including, but not limited to posts and text messages, when an individual supplies a photo, when an individual voluntarily completes a checkmyemails.co survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by checkmyemails.co or third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used in this policy, "online" means using the Internet, including the Website, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, checkmyemails.co or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to checkmyemails.co, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, photo, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). checkmyemails.co may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this Web Site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to checkmyemails.co or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from checkmyemails.co or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to checkmyemails.co. 

1.2 Third Party List Information. 

Checkmyemails.co may collect information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and checkmyemails.co subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, checkmyemails.co seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to checkmyemails.co and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list. 

1.3 Other Information. 

Other occasions when checkmyemails.co obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by checkmyemails.co or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through checkmyemails.co's customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a checkmyemails.co service or newsletter (together, "Other Information"). 

1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. 

Checkmyemails.co currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, checkmyemails.co may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information"). 

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows checkmyemails.co to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in checkmyemails.co's database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com

. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website. 

(b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an programming function (see http://truste.org

for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows checkmyemails.co to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, checkmyemails.co might place, with the consent of a Third Party website, a web beacon on the Third Party's website where baseball products are sold. When Joe, an individual listed in checkmyemails.co's database, visits the baseball website, checkmyemails.co receives notice by means of the web beacon that Joe visited the baseball site, and checkmyemails.co would then update Joe's profile with the information that Joe is interested in baseball. checkmyemails.co may thereafter present offers of baseball related products and services to Joe. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, checkmyemails.co also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in checkmyemails.co's database. 

(c) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including search engine indexing, cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is checkmyemails.co's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, checkmyemails.co strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology. 

1.5 Outside Information. 

Checkmyemails.co may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of checkmyemails.co including information located in public databases ("Outside Information"). 

1.6 Individual Information. 

As used in this policy, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information checkmyemails.co gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data. 

1.7 No Information Collected from Children. 

Checkmyemails.co does not knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If checkmyemails.co obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, checkmyemails.co has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. checkmyemails.co has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). 

1.8 Log File Information. 

When users log-in to access their account, our servers may automatically record and archive certain information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a Website. These server logs may include information vital to validating the user's authorization to access the account. Information, such as a web request, Internet Protocol (the "IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize a user's entry and activity on the Website. 

1.9 Credit Card Information. 

Checkmyemails.co may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from checkmyemails.co. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to checkmyemails.co, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. checkmyemails.co will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing user-initiated purchase transactions, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. 

2\. Use of Individual Information. 

THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION HOWEVER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION WILL NEVER BE SOLD TO THIRD PARTIES FOR MARKETING PURPOSES. 

2.1 Solicited Email. 

Checkmyemails.co only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Website to receive email from Checkmyemails.co or to individuals who have agreed on Third Party websites toreceive email from Third Parties such as Checkmyemails.co. Checkmyemails.co does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Checkmyemails.co's email messages. 

2.2 Storage of Individual Information. 

Checkmyemails.co stores the Individual Information in a database on Checkmyemails.co computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss,misuse, and alteration of the information under Checkmyemails.co's control. Notwithstanding such measures, Checkmyemails.co cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Checkmyemails.co computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered. 

3\. Dissemination of Individual Information. 

3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties. 

CHECKMYEMAILS.CO MAY SELL, LICENSE OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN CHECKMYEMAILS.CO's SOLE DISCRETION. 

3.2 Order Fulfillment. 

Checkmyemails.co will transfer Individual Information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such Third Party while using checkmyemails.co web sites or when responding to offers provided by checkmyemails.co. 

3.3 Legal Process. 

Checkmyemails.co may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities. 

3.4 Summary Data. 

Checkmyemails.co may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 

3.5 Access. 

Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting legal@checkmyemails.co. checkmyemails.co may also grant advertising clients and email services providers' access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected. 

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties. 

4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. 

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. checkmyemails.co does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and checkmyemails.co has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

4.2 Links. 

The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. checkmyemails.co is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. checkmyemails.co does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

4.3 Affiliated Companies. 

Checkmyemails.co may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with checkmyemails.co in checkmyemails.co's discretion. California residents have the right to opt-out of allowing checkmyemails.co to do any of the acts in the sentence above by sending an opt out request to legal@checkmyemails.co. Should checkmyemails.co be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, checkmyemails.co reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from the Website. 

4.4. Services. 

Checkmyemails.co may utilize various services provided by Google. By using Checkmyemails.co, you accept and agree to Google's Privacy Policy, found at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

5\. Individuals Outside of the United States. 

Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by checkmyemails.co in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States. 

6\. Unsubscribe Procedures. 

6.1 If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from checkmyemails.co, you have several options: 

a) Unsubscribe from one email list. To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) send an email to legal@checkmyemails.co or (2) follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by checkmyemails.co. 

b) Unsubscribe from all of checkmyemails.co's email lists. We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by checkmyemails.co. To globally unsubscribe from all of checkmyemails.co's lists, send an email to legal@checkmyemails.co

7\. Security. 

Checkmyemails.co has implemented commercially reasonable measures in an effect to prevent loss, misuse, and alteration of Individual Information used in our business and on the Web Site. However, no information transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of any Individual Information collected, used, or transferred under this Privacy Policy. 

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov. If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at legal@checkmyemails.co. 

California User Consumer Rights. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.
